In [music] most years, finishing the
season with five straight wins would
mean a lot.
It's hard to process a season that ended
with a 9 and 8 record when you consider
[music]
that the eighth loss came in the 12th
game. It felt like one of those years
where you end up with a top five pick.
[music] It felt like one of those
seasons that just doesn't happen very
often where the wheels completely fall
off.
And the strangest [music]
part is as the wheels were in the
process of falling off, they found a way
to push them back on
and they win five straight games.
>> [music]
>> There was a lot of work [music] that was
done without any reward. There was a lot
of goals that were set to pull ourselves
out of the doldrums of where [music] we
were at at 4 and 8 without any gift. I
think we can use that. We didn't get
anything out of that, but I promise you
we're going to use that for when we
inevitably get to where we want to get
to.
The foundation of any [music] program is
winning.
And if you can relentlessly pursue
winning [music] no matter the
circumstances, Make no mistake, this
chapter, all right, this five-week
chapter getting back to 9 and 8, all
right, this is going to be a major
chapter of the final story of where
we're headed. And we got to know where
we're going. It's going to be all about
remembering these moments as a team cuz
there's a lot to build on from here. One
more when you instill that into [music]
the organization from the top down,
in theory that can bear fruit in later
[music] years. But the fact that five in
a row can come when the cause is lost
has to have some [music] value moving
forward.
When the team made the surprising
decision weeks after the season ended to
fire GM Kwesi Adofo-Mensah, the first
question that everyone had was, well,
who's the new GM going to be? And it was
a surprise to hear there won't be one,
at least until after the draft. But when
you consider how long Rob Brzezinski has
been there, and if you assume that he
will be able to build a consensus
between the scouts and the coaches to
make the right decisions with free
agency, with the cap dollars, with the
draft picks, we can get what I think
every team needs to be successful, which
is alignment. You know, there's a
there's a head coach, there's a head
administrator, and there's a head
personnel person, and
everybody needs to work in tandem.
What's up, brother? I mean, people think
that this business is about a general
manager identifying players on his or
her own. It doesn't work that way. It's
We have 10 or 12 scouts looking at every
player and you're building a consensus,
and that's how you make good decisions.
And I just want to be a small part of
helping deliver
a championship to our fans. They've been
waiting a really, really long time, and
it's going to mean so much to them when
it finally does happen, and it will.
Well, Rob's never really changed since
I've been here. He's been the same guy
day in and day out. He approaches it the
same way. Um he has a process that he
sticks to. I've known him um, you know,
since the beginning of my career. Uh
great guy. The people here, I'm sure, I
mean,
um have seen the the best of him and the
things that he can do um outside of
that. So, I'm excited to see to see what
he does. I think his work work just
speaks for itself in all these years
he's been here. The most important thing
any sports team that hopes to be
successful can have is alignment. And if
alignment can arise this off-season, the
results will show that.
How are the holes going to be filled?
[music] How are the weaknesses going to
be made into strengths? And it's just a
matter of infusing the right [music]
players to allow the coaches to get the
most out of their abilities with the
guys who [music] are on the field doing
the things that the coaches know if we
have the guys who can do them well, it
will work and [music] the team will win.
>> Yeah, I'm excited, man. I I think we
have a a really good group. The
atmosphere is way like different. It's
different than any other places you've
ever been at. Let's get it, you know?
Let's go. There going to be free agent
options out there.
Any free agent quarterback who wants to
play
is going to want [music] to know
that he'll have a full and fair
opportunity to compete for the job.
And he's going to have to have the
confidence that he can win the job.
The Vikings need to make sure whoever
comes in understands
that you are going to get a fair [music]
opportunity and the best player is going
to play.
Another quarterback comes in and we have
a competition [music]
and we see how the players respond. We
see what the coaches think.
>> [music]
>> We see what happens when it's time to go
out and have live reps in preseason
games, and then decisions are made about
who the best steward of the offense is
[music]
going forward.
You know, I look forward to coming in
and competing, getting to learn the
offense, getting to be with uh Coach
O'Connell. Genuine genuine fandom.
Uh very, you know, ran deep. Vikings
gear through and through.
Um a lot of purple in my household. Um I
know what my skill set brings to the
game. I know what I'm capable of. Uh and
I think that um
you know, again, I'm like I said, I'm
ready to come in and compete. Just
watching from afar what KOC's been able
to do with quarterbacks, offense,
uh the guys in place here,
uh B Flo on the defense. I think that uh
it's a great fit. And like I said, I'm
thankful. I'm thankful for the
opportunity. Um I can't wait to get to
work.